BOY SUGIJAKKO

sugijakkoboy@gmail.com | boysugi20.github.io

ABOUT ME

An individual with 2+ years of experience working, developing, and maintaining web applications used in a renowned world class university as a system analyst. Keen in learning new things and eager to share that knowledge with others. Capable of performing well both individually and as part of a team. A committed, hard worker, responsible, loyal, and always have passion in the work done.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2022 - PRESENT

SENIOR SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Manage project timeline
- Design applications that are efficient to improve user experience and reduce system load
- Provide documentation

OCT 2021 - OCT 2022

SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Debug, fix, or enhance Stored Procedures used in application to fetch data from database
- Analyze requirements based on user needs
- Collaborate with programmers to develop new features
- Collaborate with programmers to enhance application to fit new user needs
- Trace errors caused by incorrect data on database

MAR 2020 - OCT 2021

JUNIOR SYSTEM ANALYST, BINA NUSANTARA IT DIVISION

- Collaborate with programmers to debug applications
- Help seniors on solving errors
- Help users with problems on application usage

EDUCATION

JUN 2022 - PRESENT

MA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY (3.88 GPA)

Thesis title: "Lightweight Face Recognition-Based Portable Attendance System With Liveness Detection"

SEP 2018 – JUN 2022

BA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY (3.74 GPA)

Thesis title: "Masked Face Recognition for a Lightweight School Attendance Management System during COVID-19 Pandemic"

SKILLS

- SQL
- Python
- Database
- Information Technology

- System Testing
- System Analysis
- Analytical Skills
- Internet of Things